<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.audio.radiogarden" 
       name="Radio Garden" 
       version="2.0" 
       provider-name="@TrainAgain2">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
        <provides>audio</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Listen to radio stations from around the world</summary>
        <summary lang="pt_BR">Ouça estações de rádio de todo o mundo</summary>
        <summary lang="ro_RO">Ascultați posturi de radio din întreaga lume</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Radio Garden allows you to explore and listen to live radio stations from around the world. Created by @TrainAgain2.</description>
        <description lang="pt_BR">O Radio Garden permite explorar e ouvir estações de rádio ao vivo de todo o mundo. Criado por @TrainAgain2.</description>
        <description lang="ro_RO">Radio Garden vă permite să explorați și să ascultați posturi de radio în direct din întreaga lume. Creat de @TrainAgain2.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">This addon uses the unofficial Radio Garden API. The author is not affiliated with Radio Garden BV.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Este addon usa a API não oficial do Radio Garden. O autor não é afiliado à Radio Garden BV.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Acest supliment folosește API-ul neoficial Radio Garden. Autorul nu este afiliat cu Radio Garden BV.</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
        <website>https://radio.garden/</website>
        <source>https://github.com/yourusername/plugin.audio.radiogarden</source>
        <news>v1.4.1 (2026-01-28)
- Fixed Icon and Fanart display issues: simplified file names for better Kodi compatibility
- Updated provider and description: Created by @TrainAgain2
- New modern artwork: updated icon and fanart with a clean white background and brush-stroke style
- Colors updated to match the original Radio Garden green and blue palette
- Removed "Popular Stations" menu as requested
- Enhanced search logic: improved accuracy and global coverage for countries and cities
- Optimized search for Portuguese speakers with expanded country name translations
- Maintained consistent use of plugin icon for all stations
- Simplified main menu for a cleaner experience
        </news>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
