<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.vidscr"
       name="Vidscr"
       version="1.4.27"
       provider-name="Zeus768">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.22.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.resolveurl" version="5.1.0" optional="true"/>
        <import addon="inputstream.adaptive" version="2.0.0" optional="true"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <summary lang="en_GB">Vidscr — Movies &amp; TV via TMDB + Vidsrc (by Zeus768)</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">A clean, simple Movies &amp; TV Shows addon. Browse new releases, Oscar nominees, genres, actors, networks and a 7-day premiering calendar. Posters and metadata from TMDB; streams sourced from vidsrcme.ru (with optional vidsrc.xyz / 2embed secondary), built-in resolvers, server sub-picker, per-show quality memory, Trakt scrobbling, watched/resume indicators and 10-second stall auto-fallback.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
        <news>v1.4.27 — MENU ICON PLACEHOLDERS. Every main-menu and submenu directory now ships a per-action placeholder PNG under resources/menu_icons/ (55 icons covering Movies / TV / Search / My Lists / Trakt / SIMKL / Bingebase / pagination). The picker is fully automatic — `add_dir(...)` resolves the icon from the `action` (+`kind` for trakt_list / simkl_list variants) via `common.menu_icon()`. To customise: drop a same-named PNG into resources/menu_icons/ (e.g. `movies_new.png`, `trakt_watchlist.png`) — Kodi picks up the override on the next nav refresh, no restart needed. Full key-to-file mapping documented in resources/menu_icons/README.md. Adding a new menu key is one line in _ACTION_ICON_MAP. Existing call sites that passed `art={'icon': ICON, ...}` are auto-detected so the new resolver still wins (legacy default-icon overrides are ignored). All previous v1.4.26 fixes carry forward (Cloudnestra DNS failover, Stigstream 25s timeout, Goojara token-gated search, extras urlencode import restored, Bingebase folder, Trakt 100-per-page pagination + personal-list context menu).</news>
        <news>v1.4.24 — TWO NEW SOURCE LAYERS at the bottom of the picker. (1) Goojara scraper added under fh/goojara.py — pulls Wootly / Luluvdo / Doodstream candidates from ww1.goojara.to and routes them through script.module.resolveurl at play time. (2) NEW PACKAGE resources/lib/extras/ — community file-host indexer aggregator that runs 15 independent sites in parallel: anymovies, bluray7, bnwmovies, bstsrs, fzmovies, hollymoviehd, levidia, myvideolinks, naijavault, projectfreetv, seriesloaded, stagatv, tvmovieflix, tvseries.in, tvseries.video. Every stream emitted by either layer is forced to sort_weight=999 (bottom of the picker) — Cloudnestra / Vidnest / Stigstream / Secondary direct-stream tiers are not touched in any way; their .m3u8 / .mp4 URLs continue to sit on top of the link list and never flow through ResolveURL. New toggle: Settings -> Sources -> "Enable extra community indexer sources" (default ON). Implementation note: extras/__init__.py is a single thread-pool runner with per-site progress callbacks, dependency helpers consolidated under extras/_helpers/, no upstream branding retained.</news>
        <news>v1.4.22 — NEW SOURCE TIER: file-host scrapers (independent 5th source). Added a parallel file-host aggregator (resources/lib/filehosts.py) that walks every scraper in resources/lib/fh/* simultaneously. Each scraper site returns Filemoon / Voe / Mixdrop / Streamtape / Streamwish / Doodstream URLs which are resolved at play time via script.module.resolveurl (optional dependency — a missing install shows a clear notification instead of crashing). Picker UX: every file-host stream is forced to the BOTTOM of the link list so existing direct .m3u8 / .mp4 streams from Cloudnestra / Vidnest / Stigstream stay on top. New setting: Sources -> "Enable file-host sources" (default ON). Initial scrapers: MoviesFree.cv (dedicated) + generic fmovie-core WordPress plugin scraper (covers Ghostplayer.store and any future mirror — adding a new site is one line in fh/fmovie_core.py's HOSTS tuple). Cloudnestra / Stigstream / Vidnest paths are completely untouched and continue returning direct URLs that never flow through ResolveURL.</news>
        <news>v1.4.19 — Added Ophim as Vidnest backend #8 (route: new.vidnest.fun/klikxxi/movie/{tmdb}). After v1.4.18 was built, Vidnest expanded their bundle from 7 to 11 backend definitions - I rechecked their site, confirmed 8 are functional (the other 3 either need a proxy config we cannot supply or are duplicate AllMovies endpoints). Net effect: 1 additional working backend per title - small but free. The progress dialog now shows 8/8 rather than 7/7. NOTE on direct-movies.com, Cineby, Nontongo investigation: direct-movies.com is SEO bait with no actual streaming content. Cineby's backend (backend.cineby.sc) is WebSocket-only and returns 403 to all HTTP endpoints - would need full WS protocol reverse-engineering. Nontongo has an encrypted payload format similar to Vidnest BUT their decryption JS is gated by origin/IP checks that block static scrapers. Same story for 2embed.cc, multiembed, vidking, fmovies-hd, 111movies, vidsrc.in, autoembed, consumet, moviesapi.to - all either Cloudflare-blocked, geo-locked, dead, or wrap the same backends Vidnest already aggregates. The 2026 free-streaming landscape has consolidated; there is no undiscovered easy-API equivalent to Vidnest. Best path forward for more reliability: smart auto-pick that races stream segments and starts on whichever responds fastest.</news>
        <news>v1.4.18 — TRAKT / SIMKL / BINGEBASE TRACKING FIX.</news>
        <news>v1.4.17 — NEW SOURCE: Vidnest multi-backend (vidnest.fun). Reverse-engineered the site's encrypted JSON envelope and now queries SEVEN independent providers in PARALLEL — MoviesAPI, PurStream, AllMovies, CatFlix, HollyMovieHD, FlixHQ and VidLink — merging every working HLS / MP4 stream into the source list. NEW: live per-source progress dialog. Toggle: Settings -> Sources -> "Enable Vidnest multi-backend" (on by default).</news>
        <news>v1.4.16 — DEPENDENCY FIX: embedded pure-Python AES-256-GCM and ChaCha20-Poly1305 (resources/lib/purecrypto.py) — verified against NIST AES-GCM and RFC 7539 test vectors. Stigstream now works on every Kodi install regardless of which crypto modules are present.</news>
        <news>v1.4.14 — NEW SOURCE: Stigstream (stigstream.ru). Reverse-engineered the site's doubly-encrypted JSON API (outer AES-256-GCM, inner ChaCha20-Poly1305, both keyed via HKDF-SHA512 from a 32-byte master extracted from the public JS bundle), then queries 8 of its regional servers IN PARALLEL and merges every working stream into the source list.</news>
        <news>v1.4.8 — FIX (Trakt / SIMKL / Bingebase OAuth): token is now persisted to BOTH the addon settings (primary) and the local JSON file (backup). HTTP 409 ("code already used") is now handled. New "Show token status" debug actions confirm exactly what is stored.</news>
        <news>v1.1.0 — Trakt scrobbling, watched / resume indicators, 10s stall auto-fallback. Secondary source toggle, server sub-picker, per-show quality memory.</news>
    </extension>
</addon>
